export const usGov2305Data = {
    "mindtap":{
        "Chapter 1":[
            {
              "Question": "What is the current federal minimum wage?",
              "Answer": "$7.25"
            },
            {
              "Question": "What is the federal poverty level income for an individual?",
              "Answer": "$12,140"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Which of the following can bring a full-time worker into poverty?",
              "Answer": "Both of these"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Which of the following viewpoints explains support for increasing the minimum wage?",
              "Answer": "Full-time workers are at risk of living in poverty."
            },
            {
              "Question": "Which of the following viewpoints explains opposition to increasing the minimum wage?",
              "Answer": "Jobs will be lost because employers will direct their money to paying higher wages."
            },
            {
              "Question": "The desire of citizens to be protected from any abuses of governmental power stems from their value of",
              "Answer": "liberty."
            },
            {
              "Question": "Critics of pluralism see public policy as",
              "Answer": "only satisfying the interests of the largest groups."
            },
            {
              "Question": "As an ongoing organization that performs certain functions for society and has a life separate from the lives of the individuals who are part of it, a government can be categorized as a type of",
              "Answer": "institution."
            },
            {
              "Question": "What is typically most valued by American conservatives?",
              "Answer": "Patriotism and traditional values"
            },
            {
              "Question": "The United States government is an example of a",
              "Answer": "representative democracy."
            },
            {
              "Question": "What most helps predict the future population levels?",
              "Answer": "Total fertility rate"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Greta lives in a country where all political, social, and economic decisions are strictly controlled by the government. She knows and abides by these decisions whether she agrees with them or not. The government in Greta's country represents which type of regime?",
              "Answer": "Totalitarianism"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Sean supports the government's actions to promote economic equality and also to defend traditional family values. Which label of the four-cornered ideological grid best describes Sean's political leaning?",
              "Answer": "Economic liberal, cultural conservative"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Initiatives and referenda are both instances in which",
              "Answer": "voters have a role in making law."
            },
            {
              "Question": "One of the original purposes of government is the maintenance of order. Which scenario is an example of providing order?",
              "Answer": "A government which works to protect society from violence and crime."
            },
            {
              "Question": "Which description best defines a democracy?",
              "Answer": "A system of government in which political authority is vested in the people"
            },
            {
              "Question": "In a democracy that supports majoritarianism, the government ought to do what the majority of the people want. Which example is at odds with this theory and would suggest that this democracy does not support majoritarianism principles?",
              "Answer": "Country B tries to keep religion out of public schools, despite broad public support."
            },
            {
              "Question": "Which right is considered a civil liberty?",
              "Answer": "Freedom of speech"
            },
            {
              "Question": "The struggle over power or influence within organizations or informal groups that can grant benefits or privileges best defines",
              "Answer": "politics."
            },
            {
              "Question": "Which political ideology is based on skepticism or opposition toward most government activities?",
              "Answer": "Libertarianism"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Promoting equality often requires limiting the right to treat people unequally.",
              "Answer": "TRUE"
            },
            {
              "Question": "In recent years, there has been a small degree of overlap between ideological principles, such as progressivism and conservatism, and the two major political parties.",
              "Answer": "FALSE"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Currently, what is the largest minority group in the United States?",
              "Answer": "Latino Americans"
            },
            {
              "Question": "The notion that the United States is actually a \"sham democracy\" fits with which perspective?",
              "Answer": "Elite theory"
            },
            {
              "Question": "At the start of each school day, Julio's class stands and recites the Pledge of Allegiance while facing the flag. His teacher has instructed everyone to place their hands over their hearts while reciting the pledge. This part of Julio's day can be considered political socialization.",
              "Answer": "TRUE"
            },
            {
              "Question": "The capitalist system of the United States is based on",
              "Answer": "private property rights."
            },
            {
              "Question": "The collection of values, customs, and language established by the group or groups that traditionally have controlled politics and government in a society best defines which type of culture?",
              "Answer": "Dominant"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Liberalism and conservatism are examples of political cultures.",
              "Answer": "FALSE"
            },
            {
              "Question": "When a government has the power to make laws and enforce its decisions but lacks the broad support of the people to do so, it can be said to have legitimacy but not authority.",
              "Answer": "FALSE"
            },
            {
              "Question": "The Supreme Court has held that the government cannot ban abortion or private homosexual behavior based on the right to",
              "Answer": "privacy."
            }
          ],
          "Chapter 2":[
            {
              "Question": "What tool does the Supreme Court use when it wants to adapt the Constitution to new developments?",
              "Answer": "Judicial review"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Which statement is true regarding the Three-Fifths Compromise?",
              "Answer": "It counted slaves as property."
            },
            {
              "Question": "What did the Federalists advocate?",
              "Answer": "Ratification of the new Constitution"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Why did many of the framers feel that enumerating specific civil liberties in a bill of rights was unnecessary?",
              "Answer": "The Constitution already included certain rights."
            },
            {
              "Question": "In the federal system established by the founders, sovereign powers were to be",
              "Answer": "divided between the states and the national government."
            },
            {
              "Question": "Shays' Rebellion demonstrated that the American central government",
              "Answer": "could not protect the citizenry from armed rebellion."
            },
            {
              "Question": "Although the New Jersey Plan was ultimately rejected at the Constitutional Convention, one of its proposals that was retained in the new constitution was",
              "Answer": "the supremacy doctrine."
            },
            {
              "Question": "Historian Charles Beard believed that the Constitution was produced primarily to protect the civil liberties of the people.",
              "Answer": "False"
            },
            {
              "Question": "By the time the Second Continental Congress met, fighting had broken out between the British and the colonists; as a result, one of the main actions of the Second Continental Congress was to",
              "Answer": "establish an army."
            },
            {
              "Question": "The delegates to the Constitutional Convention represented a large variety of interests, professions, and levels of wealth.",
              "Answer": "FALSE"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Young Benjamin is learning about colonial times. As he reads a passage from the Declaration of Independence stating that all Men have the rights to \"Life, Liberty, and the Pursuit of Happiness,\" he realizes he's already learned about this concept from the writings of John Locke. Benjamin understands that the Declaration is referring to",
              "Answer": "natural rights."
            },
            {
              "Question": "The proposal of a legislature based solely on representation proportional to population was a key feature of",
              "Answer": "the Virginia Plan."
            },
            {
              "Question": "The Mayflower Compact's historical and political significance is twofold: it depended on the consent of the affected individuals, and it served as",
              "Answer": "a prototype for similar compacts in American history."
            },
            {
              "Question": "The Jamestown colonists set a political precedent by",
              "Answer": "instituting a representative assembly."
            },
            {
              "Question": "What is one formal method of proposing and ratifying a Constitutional Amendment?",
              "Answer": "It must be proposed by two-thirds vote in both houses of Congress and ratified by a positive vote of three-fourths of state legislatures."
            },
            {
              "Question": "The Bill of Rights can be referred to as a \"bill of limits\" because it essentially",
              "Answer": "limits the powers of the national government over the rights and liberties of individuals."
            },
            {
              "Question": "In the summer of 1776, Thomas Jefferson began writing the first drafts of what document, in order to separate from Britain?",
              "Answer": "The Declaration of Independence"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Betsey has been elected by the voters of her state to serve as an elector. In the upcoming election, she feels this responsibility is more important than ever, as most people are too swayed by political advertising or interest group affiliations. Betsey realizes the modern purpose of the electoral college is to",
              "Answer": "make the presidency completely independent of Congress."
            },
            {
              "Question": "As a consequence of the Boston Tea Party, the British government passed the Coercive Acts, which closed Boston Harbor and gave the British direct control of the Massachusetts government.",
              "Answer": "TRUE"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Despite losing the fight over Constitutional ratification, the Anti-Federalists did make a strong and successful case for the inclusion of",
              "Answer": "a bill of rights."
            },
            {
              "Question": "At the Constitutional Convention, a major point of debate among the delegates was whether to",
              "Answer": "create a strong national government."
            },
            {
              "Question": "The Constitution is a rigid document and cannot be interpreted to adapt to new social and political realities. The only way to change it is through amendments.",
              "Answer": "FALSE"
            },
            {
              "Question": "The early colonists sought to create a weak central government with a voluntary association of independent states that agreed to only limited restraints on their freedom of action, forming a",
              "Answer": "confederation."
            },
            {
              "Question": "As John Locke argued, an agreement among the people to form a government and abide by its rules is a type of",
              "Answer": "social contract."
            },
            {
              "Question": "While the early colonists were governed by the British, they were so far away from London that they exercised a large measure of self-government, including",
              "Answer": "making their own laws."
            }
          ],
          "Chapter 3":[
            {
              "Question": "Where are reserved powers found in the U.S. Constitution?",
              "Answer": "Tenth Amendment"
            },
            {
              "Question": "What are reserved powers?",
              "Answer": "The powers of the states"
            },
            {
              "Question": "In which case did the U.S. Supreme Court determine that the federal government did not overstep its bounds under the commerce clause when it enacted the Controlled Substances Act of 1970?",
              "Answer": "Gonzalez v. Raich"
            },
            {
              "Question": "According to the U.S. Supreme Court, which congressional power may be used by Congress to regulate local activities?",
              "Answer": "Commerce"
            },
            {
              "Question": "For what purpose(s) has marijuana been legalized at the state level?",
              "Answer": "Both medical and recreational use"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Which is an important clause governing interstate relations?",
              "Answer": "Extend to other states' citizens the privileges and immunities of its own citizens"
            },
            {
              "Question": "No state is allowed to enter into a treaty on its own with another country. This is an example of which type of power?",
              "Answer": "Prohibited power"
            },
            {
              "Question": "The Constitution grants Congress the power to do whatever is necessary to execute its enumerated or expressed powers. This is referred to as",
              "Answer": "the elastic clause."
            },
            {
              "Question": "What are the terms of authority in a federal political system?",
              "Answer": "It is divided between the central government and constituent governments."
            },
            {
              "Question": "In its McCulloch v. Maryland decision, the U.S. Supreme Court determined that",
              "Answer": "the federal government had implied power related to its designated power."
            },
            {
              "Question": "Dual federalism is a doctrine that emphasizes",
              "Answer": "a distinction between federal and state authority."
            },
            {
              "Question": "Which Amendment to the Constitution abolished the institution of slavery?",
              "Answer": "Thirteenth"
            },
            {
              "Question": "In United States v. Windsor, the Supreme Court found that the federal government must recognize same-sex marriages that were approved by the state in which they occurre",
              "Answer": "TRUE"
            },
            {
              "Question": "In a confederal system of government, the central government—created by a league of independent states—has what type of powers over the states?",
              "Answer": "Only limited"
            },
            {
              "Question": "The state of Alabama prohibits gambling, but the state of Ohio allows it. This is an example of what type of power?",
              "Answer": "Police power"
            },
            {
              "Question": "In a unitary system of government, ultimate authority rests with the states or provinces, while under federalism, all power lies with the national or central government.",
              "Answer": "FALSE"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Which is considered an enumerated power granted by the Constitution to the national government?",
              "Answer": "The power to make uniform naturalization laws"
            },
            {
              "Question": "In Illinois, French cheese sold at a grocery store is subject to state taxes as well as an nationally-imposed import tax. This is an example of",
              "Answer": "concurrent powers."
            },
            {
              "Question": "The Fourteenth Amendment led to the Bill of Rights being applied to state governments.",
              "Answer": "TRUE"
            },
            {
              "Question": "The states and national government were distinct under dual federalism but mixed in their powers, responsibilities, and finances under",
              "Answer": "cooperative federalism."
            },
            {
              "Question": "Which president was responsible for the wave of devolution that was called \"New Federalism\"?",
              "Answer": "Richard Nixon"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Which of the following was an issue before the Supreme Court in Gibbons v. Ogden (1824)?",
              "Answer": "Whether the power to regulate interstate commerce was a concurrent power"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Jenna benefits from a state welfare program designed to assist mothers with dependent children. The funding is provided by the national government specifically for welfare, but her state administers the funds. This is an example of what type of grant?",
              "Answer": "Categorical grant"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Danny works for the Surface Transportation Program for his state. He helps ensure that these general funds provided by the Federal Highway Administration go toward the most pressing transportation needs identified in his state. This is an example of a(n)",
              "Answer": "block grant."
            },
            {
              "Question": "When the government raises funds through taxation or borrowing, and then spends these funds, it is implementing",
              "Answer": "fiscal policy."
            },
            {
              "Question": "A federal mandate is a requirement in federal legislation that forces states to comply with certain rules.",
              "Answer": "TRUE"
            },
            {
              "Question": "As a practical solution to the main issue at the Constitutional Convention, federalism was adopted because it established a strong national government and",
              "Answer": "retained state traditions and local power."
            },
            {
              "Question": "The fact that the United States is a sovereign power among nations, and so its national government must be the only government that deals with other nations, is the principle behind",
              "Answer": "inherent powers."
            },
            {
              "Question": "Devolution refers to the transfer of powers from a",
              "Answer": "central government to a state or local government."
            },
            {
              "Question": "The supremacy clause serves to protect the authority of",
              "Answer": "the federal government."
            }
          ],
          "Chapter 4":[
            {
              "Question": "For which ailments has marijuana achieved medical benefits?",
              "Answer": "Treating cancer"
            },
            {
              "Question": "To what has the medical marijuana debate been compared?",
              "Answer": "Prohibition"
            },
            {
              "Question": "What proportion of states have some sort of marijuana access laws?",
              "Answer": "Nearly all"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Which of the following concerns opponents of medical marijuana use?",
              "Answer": "People without medical ailments will claim to have them in order to procure marijuan"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Does the federal government consider the use of marijuana to be a crime?",
              "Answer": "Yes"
            },
            {
              "Question": "For criminal suspects held in custody by the police, Miranda rights allow the suspect the right to",
              "Answer": "remain silent."
            },
            {
              "Question": "Shortly after the September 11, 2001 terrorist attacks, President George W. Bush issued an executive order allowing which agency to conduct secret surveillance without court warrants?",
              "Answer": "National Security Agency"
            },
            {
              "Question": "The standard used to determine if damages can be obtained from a libelous statement made about a public official is",
              "Answer": "actual malice."
            },
            {
              "Question": "The first act in a criminal proceeding is an arraignment in which the defendant is brought before a court to",
              "Answer": "enter a plea of guilty or not guilty."
            },
            {
              "Question": "In a series of rulings dealing with the establishment clause, which has the Supreme Court clearly established?",
              "Answer": "Prohibited religious prayers in public schools"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Publishing truths that harm a person's reputation and livelihood is considered to be defamation of character.",
              "Answer": "FALSE"
            },
            {
              "Question": "In testing the constitutionality of government aid to religious schools, the Supreme Court imposes the Lemon test.",
              "Answer": "TRUE"
            },
            {
              "Question": "A local newspaper writes a lengthy expose about the mayor, hinting that she is an alcoholic who is often found sleeping on the joIn fact, these allegations are ultimately are proven false, but the rumors persist in the community. This newspaper might be accused of",
              "Answer": "libel."
            },
            {
              "Question": "Susan was punished for an act she committed in 1980, but it was not illegal at the time when she committed it. What is this an example of?",
              "Answer": "Ex post facto law"
            },
            {
              "Question": "The Bill of Rights, as originally intended, limited the powers of the national government only and did not apply to state governments.",
              "Answer": "TRUE"
            },
            {
              "Question": "What civil liberty is listed in the Bill of Rights, rather than the Constitution?",
              "Answer": "Congress shall make no law respecting an establishment of religion."
            },
            {
              "Question": "The unconstitutional act of restricting expression before it occurs is called",
              "Answer": "prior restraint."
            },
            {
              "Question": "Freedom of religion rests upon two distinct principles, which are the",
              "Answer": "establishment and free exercise clauses."
            },
            {
              "Question": "In which situations are roving wire taps allowed to be used for a person under suspicion to be monitored electronically?",
              "Answer": "No matter what form of electronic communication he or she uses"
            },
            {
              "Question": "What is the Supreme Court's current ruling on the death penalty?",
              "Answer": "The Supreme Court has allowed the states to enact more precise laws regarding the death penalty."
            },
            {
              "Question": "A church in Texas secretly endorses and makes substantial contributions to a political candidate's campaign. Another candidate reports this to the election commission, and IRS investigates and intervenes. Which aspect of the First Amendment does this demonstrate?",
              "Answer": "Constraints of the free exercise clause"
            },
            {
              "Question": "In Gideon v. Wainwright (1963), the Supreme Court held that if a person is accused of a felony and cannot afford an attorney, an attorney must be made available to the accused person",
              "Answer": "at the government's expense."
            },
            {
              "Question": "Which statement best describes how Supreme Court decisions have impacted abortion laws in the United States since the landmark case Roe v. Wade essentially legalized abortion in 1973?",
              "Answer": "Partial birth abortion has been restricte"
            },
            {
              "Question": "The right to privacy is a unique civil liberty in that it is never explicitly mentioned in the Constitution and is dependent on an interpretation of several other civil liberties.",
              "Answer": "TRUE"
            },
            {
              "Question": "What has allowed more than 150 prisoners since 1973 to be released after they were wrongfully convicted of murder?",
              "Answer": "DNA evidence"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Based on a series of Supreme Court rulings, the most restrictions on free speech generally allowed under the Constitution are",
              "Answer": "at a high school."
            },
            {
              "Question": "A defendant's pretrial rights include",
              "Answer": "the right to remain silent."
            },
            {
              "Question": "The \"clear and present danger\" test is used to determine when it is permissible to restrict",
              "Answer": "freedom of speech."
            },
            {
              "Question": "José is a legal immigrant in the U.S., but he is not a citizen. Which statement about rights applies to him?",
              "Answer": "He receives due process under law according to the Fourteenth Amendment, and protections afforded by the Bill of Rights."
            },
            {
              "Question": "Davis is pulled over for a minor traffic violation. While he is receiving a ticket, the police officer checks the phone in Davis' backpack because he's in the vicinity of a recent break-in, and the officer thinks he \"looks guilty.\" Later, this illegally seized evidence is ruled inadmissible because of protections provided by",
              "Answer": "the exclusionary rule."
            }
          ]
        }
}